castle.com 2017-08-02

# Privacy Policy – castle.com

[](http://castle.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/07/privacy-policy.png)At castle.com (â€œcastle.com,â€ â€œwe,â€ â€œus,â€ â€œourâ€), we know you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read on to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By visiting castle.comâ€™s website at castle.com.com or any of our other websites, applications, domain names or other linked pages, or using any of our services (collectively, the â€œServicesâ€), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. By using the Services, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.

#### **WHAT THIS IS SAYING**

Your privacy is very important to us. This policy tells you how your personal information is used after you create a castle.com account. By using castle.com, you acknowledge that youâ€™ve read and accepted these policies.

You are responsible for any Content (as that term is defined in our [Terms of Service](http://castle.com/terms-of-service/)) you provide in connection with the Services. We cannot control the actions of users with whom you or any Services subscribers may choose to share information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that Content you or any user posts on the Services will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. Although we may allow our users to set privacy options that limit access to certain parts of the Services, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable and that we are not responsible for circumvention of any security measures contained on the Services. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of Content may remain viewable in cached pages and archives or if other users have copied or stored your Content.

You may request removal of your Personal Information by contacting us at [contact@castle.com](mailto:contact@castle.com). We will remove the information that you request from our database, but this information may remain in our server logs as part of our standard backup procedures.

Any improper collection or misuse of Content or other information accessible on the Services is a violation of [castle.comâ€™s Terms of Service](http://castle.com/terms-of-service/) and should be reported to [report@castle.com](mailto:report@castle.com).

#### **WHAT THIS IS SAYING**

Please keep in mind that youâ€™re responsible for the content of your account and all your messages. You can request that your account is deleted by contacting us a [contact@castle.com](mailto:contact@castle.com), but castle.com is not responsible for what subscribers may do with your sent messages.

## **WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVER?**

This Privacy Policy explains how castle.com collects and uses information from you and other users who access or use the Services, including our treatment of personally identifiable information (â€œPersonal Informationâ€). References to â€œPersonal Informationâ€ in this Privacy Policy shall apply to personal information of individual users of the Services. Also, this Privacy Policy covers castle.comâ€™s treatment of any Personal Information that our partners share with us, or that you provide to castle.com through a third party website or service using a castle.com application. This policy does not apply to websites or services or practices of companies that we do not own or control.

#### **WHAT THIS IS SAYING**

Hereâ€™s what this policy covers: all information that you provide to us and that we collect while youâ€™re using castle.com. This policy doesnâ€™t cover 3rd party companies that we donâ€™t control but who help us operate our service. Keep reading, thereâ€™s more about this later!

## **HOW IS CHILDRENâ€™S PERSONAL INFORMATION TREATED?**

We have included some information below related to the Childrenâ€™s Online Privacy and Protection Act (â€œCOPPAâ€). COPPA requires that online service providers obtain parental consent or provide notice before they knowingly collect personally identifiable information online from children who are under 13 (â€œunder age usersâ€). Pursuant to COPPA, we may collect an underage userâ€™s name (first name and last initial), date of birth, email address and/or telephone number in order to operate and provide the castle.com Services, and we may collect the underage userâ€™s parentâ€™s (or legal guardianâ€™s) email address in order to provide notice to parents that we may contact their underage user for the purpose of providing the Services. If castle.com does not receive the parentâ€™s email address within a reasonable time period, the underage user will not be able to receive any messages and **his/her personally identifiable information will be deleted.** If an underage userâ€™s castle.com account is inactive for at least twelve months (meaning, the account has not received a message through the Services in that period of time), castle.comâ€™s policy is to delete the personally-identifiable information. If we learn we have collected Personal Information from an underage user other than pursuant to the above, or if we learn that an underage user has provided us personal information beyond what we request from him or her, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that an underage user may have provided us personal information in violation of this paragraph, please contact us at [report@castle.com](mailto:report@castle.com). ****

#### **WHAT THIS IS SAYING**

castle.com collects limited personal information from users under 13, and notifies a parent or guardian when collecting personal information from users under 13 years old. We will delete their personal information if the childâ€™s account does not have an associated email address from a parent or guardian, or if the account has been inactive for at least 12 months. Any questions or concerns? Just email us! [contact@castle.com](mailto:contact@castle.com)

## **WHAT INFORMATION DOES castle.COM DISPLAY OR COLLECT?**

When you use the Services, you may set up your personal profile, send messages, perform searches and queries, and transmit information through various channels as permitted by the functionality of the Services. castle.com will not share personal contact information between Organizers and Subscribers (as those terms are defined in [castle.comâ€™s Terms of Service](http://castle.com/terms-of-service/)) without user permission. The information we gather from users enables us to verify user identity and allows our users to set up a user account and profile through the Services, and helps us personalize and improve our services. We retain such information to provide the Services to you and our other users and to provide a useful user experience. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information.

#### **WHAT THIS IS SAYING**

Information you provide to castle.com by creating an account (or when joining a class) is used to operate our service. For example, we use this information to verify user identity and help users create an account on castle.com. castle.com will not share personal contact information, besides full names, between Organizers and Subscribers without user permission.

## **INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US:**

We receive and store any information you knowingly enter on the Services, whether via computer, mobile phone, other wireless device, or that you provide to us in any other way. This information may include Personal Information such as your name, phone number(s), email address(es), photograph(s), and, in certain circumstances, your school, club, or organization affiliation (which may be used to validate your account) or to provide you with notifications via the Services from a teacher, school and/or district, club or team (â€œNotificationsâ€), or any other information necessary for us to provide our services. For underage users, we collect a name (first name and last initial), date of birth, email address and/or telephone number, and that underage userâ€™s parentâ€™s email address, to provide notice to parents regarding the service. You may choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the Personal Information we receive about you to enable us to provide you with the Services and also for purposes such as:

  * authenticating your identity,
  * responding to your requests for certain information,
  * customizing the features that we make available to you,
  * improving internal operations (including troubleshooting, testing, and analyzing usage),
  * communicating with you about new features
  * and, most importantly, protecting our users and making sure our Services are safe and secure.

#### **WHAT THIS IS SAYING**

The information you provide to castle.com is also used to analyze usage and improve our product. We donâ€™t show or share your personal information except in the few circumstances described here. We may also review account information to protect the safety of our community.

## **INFORMATION COLLECTED AUTOMATICALLY:**

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with the Services. castle.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, castle.com cookie information, the page you requested, and other usage information such as your activity on the Services, the numbers and frequency of visitors to our site and its components (similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show). None of this information constitutes Personal Information. Certain information that is collected automatically, such as device ID and phone number, will be treated as Personal Information.

We also may provide to our partners aggregate information derived from such automatically collected information about how our users, collectively, use our site. We may share this type of non-personally identifiable, aggregated statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use our partnersâ€™ services as well as the Services.

#### **WHAT THIS IS SAYING**

There is certain information that we gather automatically when you use castle.com, such as your IP address and cookie information. We still treat this as personal information and are very careful with it.

## **WHAT ABOUT COOKIES, PIXELS AND LOCAL STORAGE?**

Cookies are small files that websites place on your computer as you browse the web. Like many websites, castle.com uses cookies to discover how people are using our Services and to make them work better.

A pixel is a small amount of code on a web page or in an email notification. As many services do, we (or our Agents) may use pixels to learn whether youâ€™ve interacted with certain of web or email content on our Services. This helps us measure and improve our Services and personalize your experience on castle.com.

Local storage is an industry-standard technology that allows a website or application to store information locally on your computer or mobile device. We use local storage to customize what we show you based on your past interactions with castle.com.

castle.com uses these technologies to deliver, measure, and improve our Services in various ways. These uses generally fall into one of the following categories:

  * **Authentication and security:**
    * To log you into castle.com.
    * To protect your security.
    * To help us detect and fight spam, abuse, and other activities that violate the castle.com Rules.
  * **Preferences:**
    * For example, these technologies help authenticate your access to castle.com and prevent unauthorized parties from accessing your account. They also let us show you appropriate content through our Services.
    * To remember information about your browser and your preferences.
  * **Analytics and research:**
    * For example, cookies may help us remember your preferred language or country that you are in. We can then provide you with castle.com content in your preferred language without having to ask you each time you visit castle.com. We can also customize content based on your country, such as disabling SMS, or to withhold certain content based on applicable local laws.
    * To help us improve and understand how people use our Services.Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because you will not be able to log in or use many of the Servicesâ€™ features without cookies enabled. Note that the use of cookies by third parties is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies.

#### **WHAT THIS IS SAYING**

For example, cookies help us test different versions of our services to see which particular features or content users prefer. We might also optimize and improve your experience on castle.com by using cookies to see how you interact with our services, such as when and how often you use them and what links you click on. We may use Google Analytics to assist us with this.

Cookies are bits of information that tell us youâ€™ve visited castle.com before and helps the browser remember things about you such as language setting. Our cookies do not collect any personal information from you. This only applies to castle.com cookies and no one elses.

## **WILL castle.COM SHARE ANY OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION IT RECEIVES?**

castle.com relies on its users to provide accurate Personal Information in order to provide our Services. We try our best to protect that information and make sure that we are responsible in handling, disclosing, and retaining your data. We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone (but remember that if other castle.com users or third parties have access to your Personal Information, they may use and share your information in ways that castle.com cannot, and does not, control). However, we share your Personal Information in personally identifiable form as described below.

### **Agents and Service Providers:**

Advertising is not permitted on the Services. However, we employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and may need to share your information with them (and for them to use that information) in order to provide aspects of our Services to you. Some examples of services for which we may use agents include sending email or SMS, analyzing data, and providing user services. These agents may use Personal Information we share with them, for example, to assist us, to provide their services to you and/or us, and to measure and improve the performance of their services.

#### **WHAT THIS IS SAYING**

castle.com does not rent or sell your personal information. We may share your information to provide certain parts of the castle.com service, only as provided in this policy. If you have any questions, please reach out to us at _contact@castle.com_.

### _Business Transfers:_

If castle.com or substantially all of its assets were acquired, user information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of castle.com may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on the Services of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. In the unlikely event that castle.com goes out of business, we will protect your information and delete your information.

#### **WHAT THIS IS SAYING**

If our company is bought by someone else, we may need to provide your information to that company. We will be sure to let you know if this ever happens.

### _Protection of castle.com and Others:_

We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to:

  * comply with the law, such as complying with a subpoena or other legal process;
  * enforce or apply our [Terms of Service](http://castle.com/terms-of-service/) and other agreements; or
  * protect the rights, property, or safety of castle.com, our employees, our users, or others. This includes, without limitation, exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection or responding to government requests.

#### **WHAT THIS IS SAYING**

We may release your personal information if necessary to protect our community (for example, to comply with legal requests).

### _With Your Consent:_

Except as set forth herein or where castle.com determines necessary in order to comply with law or legal process, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and you will be given the option to prevent the sharing of this information unless required by law or legal processes.

#### **WHAT THIS IS SAYING**

If there is any other reason we need to share your personal information (other than with our 3rd party services or for legal reasons), we will get your consent first.

## **IS INFORMATION ABOUT ME SECURE?**

If you have created a castle.com account, your account Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You may help protect against unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

castle.com endeavors to protect user information to ensure that user account information is kept private, however, we cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time. For additional information about the security measures we use in connection with the Services, please contact us at _contact@castle.com_.

#### **WHAT THIS IS SAYING**

The security of your personal information is extremely important to us and we take measures internally to make sure your information is safe with us.

## **SOCIAL MEDIA (FEATURES) AND WIDGETS**

Our Services may include social media features, such as the Facebook â€œLikeâ€ button, and widgets, such as the â€œShare thisâ€ button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Services. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## **WHAT INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS AND MODIFY?**

As a castle.com account holder, you have access to view and update the following information at your discretion:

  * information in your user account (such as your email address),
  * subscriber names,
  * user preferences,
  * organization (or school) affiliation, and
  * content in your account (note that once provided, you may not be able to edit or remove certain types of content, such as messages)
  * This list may change as the Services change.

#### **WHAT THIS IS SAYING**

You may access and change certain information that you enter into your castle.com account.

## **HOW DO I DELETE MY ACCOUNT?**

As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, even though it may be needed to take advantage of certain castle.com features.

You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in the â€œWhat Information Can I Accessâ€ section above. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. Certain types of communication you send to other users cannot be removed, such as messages.

You may request deletion of your castle.com account by emailing [contact@castle.com](mailto:contact@castle.com). Please note that certain information may remain in our records, server logs and archives after deletion of your account. castle.com retains this information for purposes such as diagnosing problems with the service and for auditing legal investigations, but reserves the right to delete this information in accordance with its standard business practices in effect from time to time. Further, information and other content you have provided may remain visible elsewhere to the extent such content was copied or stored by other users.

For under age users with an account that is inactive for twelve months or more (meaning the account has not received a message through the Services in that time), castle.comâ€™s policy is to disable access to Personal Information associated with that account.

If yours or your childâ€™s personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our Service, wish to refuse further contact by castle.com with your child, you may review, correct, update, delete inaccuracies, request deletion of your childâ€™s information, or amend it by contacting us at [contact@castle.com](mailto:contact@castle.com) or by logging into your account. We will respond to your request as quickly as possible.

We will retain yours or your childâ€™s information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide Services. If you wish to cancel yours or your childâ€™s account or request that we no longer use the information to provide Services, contact us at contact@castle.com.com. Note we will retain and use information, for example, to comply with our audit and legal obligations, to resolve disputes, and to enforce our agreements.

#### **WHAT THIS IS SAYING**

As an Organizer or teacher, you may delete your account at any time by logging in online. As a Subscriber, such as a student or parent, please email [contact@castle.com](mailto:contact@castle.com) to delete your account. Once deleted, we do keep a copy of message history and other account information for your convenience and safety. Certain accounts are fully deleted after 12 months of inactivity.

## **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (using the e-mail address specified in your account) or by posting a notice on the Services prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

If we make material changes to the types of Personal Information we collect or how we use Personal Information collected from underage users we will notify parents by email in order to obtain verifiable parental consent for the new uses of the childâ€™s Personal Information.
